IBRAHEEM ADEYEMO

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

9, Aminu Street, Mende Maryland, Ikeja, Lagos. 07035853137. aderemiibrahim11@gmail.com.

PERSONAL PROFILE

Both front end UI/UX designer and back end developer as well as a trainer. Worked with many companies across Nigeria, built inclusive web interfaces and experiences with strong focus on accessibility, mobile responsiveness, and performance. Trained beginners' web designers and developers about front end development; particularly CSS and JavaScript. Expert knowledge in React, Node.js, Redux, JQuery, APIs, Express.js, WordPress and Photoshop.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

JavaScript, React.js, Redux.js, CSS, MySQL, Node.js, Express.js, HTML, WordPress, GitHub, Python(Django).

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

→ FRONT END DEVELOPER

COUONE TECHNOLOGY LIMITED, Ogun State.

(Feb 2019 - Till date)

- Built an online donation platform to help the sick ones have quick access to funds. This project didn't only improve my visual and user experience design, but also increase my experience in collaborating with product manager and back end team.
- Worked with the front end team and collaborated with back end as well as tester
 to Build a computer based test (CBT) exam platform. The agile methodology
 implemented in the course of development of this project help to improve on the
 skill and I also learnt Sprint Planning, Retrospective as well as Stand-ups.

→ FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PROFITPOIN TECHNOLOGY, LAGOS.

(Aug 2018-Feb 2019)

- Built a portfolio website for the company. I learnt the art of designing wireframe / mockup for web project. This assisted in improving my photoshop usage and some other adobe tools such as illustrator.
- I learnt and did set up development environment as well as production environment. This is because I had to host the project on production environment using heroku.
- I did work with Git /GitHub which facilitate collaboration, versioning and project remote storage.

→ WEB DEVELOPER

SUCESSTRENDMARKETING, Port Harcourt.

(Feb 2017-Aug 2018)

- Built websites used by the company clients for their businesses. I learnt wordpress development, web hosting, website backup and API integration.
- I learnt web traffic generation using social media, SEO, paid and organic advertisement as well as web conversion.
- Facilitated Trainings, responsibility was to train the beginners developer the coding skills.

→ INDUSTRIAL TRAINING

Ladoke Akintola University Of Technology Teaching Hospital, Ogbomoso.

(2014–2015)

- Performed immunoassay metabolites research.
- Exposed to the use of physicochemical equipment such as spectrophotometer, atomic absorption spectrophotometer (AAS) and Gas Chromatography (GC).

EDUCATION

Ladoke Akintola University Of Technology (LAUTECH). (2010-2015)

Biochemistry (BTech)

PERSONAL SKILLS AND ABILITIES

- Coding
- Graphics
- Communication
- Attention to details
- Collaboration
- Project Management

PROJECTS /PORTFOLIO

- https://conjugality.herokuapp.com/
- https://profipoint.herokuapp.com/
- https://ibraheemadeyemo.herokuapp.com/

GITHUB

• https://github.com/ibraheem-adeyemo/